[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- I am so excited for the carnival this Saturday.
我对这周六的嘉年华感到非常兴奋。
- Guys! Guess what they're having at the carnival?
伙计们！猜猜嘉年华上有什么？
A Deep Fry Anything booth!
一个可以油炸任何东西的摊位！
- Will they deep fry an apple? - Yes!
他们会油炸苹果吗？ - 会！
- Will they deep fry a bologna sandwich?
他们会油炸波洛尼亚三明治吗？
- Yes! - Will they deep fry a soccer ball?
会！ - 他们会油炸足球吗？
- They will deep fry anything! It's literally in the name.
他们会油炸任何东西！这名字里就说明了。
- [scoffs]
哼
Who'd wanna deep fry a soccer ball?
谁会想油炸一个足球呢？
- You're the one who asked!
- You seem pretty angry about this fry booth thing.
- You know what?
30 seconds ago, I was around that corner thinking,
"Man, when I tell them about this deep fry booth,
they're gonna be just as excited as I am."
But you know what?
Just like that time I found a practically unused spatula
in the woods,
you ruined this as well.
- It had blood on it.
- 上面有血。
- Could've been sauce!
- 可能是酱汁！
- Okay, nobody is ruining this carnival for anybody.
- 好吧，谁也不能毁了这次嘉年华。
We have waited too long.
我们已经等得太久了。
I mean, it's finally our year to be the oldest kids at the carnival.
我的意思是，今年我们终于成了嘉年华上最大的孩子。
boys: Yeah! - I mean, since first grade,
男孩们: 是的！ - 我是说，从一年级开始，
we have looked at those older kids and thought, "Wow, I wish I was having as much fun as them."
我们看着那些大孩子，心里想，“哇，真希望我能像他们一样玩得开心。”
boys: Yeah!
男孩们: 是的！
- And this year, we are them.
- 而今年，我们就是他们。
boys: Yeah!
男孩们: 是的！
- And this year, I'm finally gonna win
今年，我终于要赢了
that stuffed banana with a face on it.
那个带脸的填充香蕉。
- What is it with you?
你怎么回事？
Every year, you blow an entire month's allowance
每年你都花掉一个月的零花钱
on game tickets trying to win that stupid banana.
买游戏票，就为了赢那个蠢香蕉。
- It's not stupid.
它不蠢。
It's wearing glasses.
它还戴着眼镜。
- Harpers.
哈珀斯。
all: Principal Tarian.
所有人：塔里安校长。
- [clears throat]
（清嗓子）
- Oh. all: Shelly.
哦，大家：Shelly。
- Shelly...
Shelly……
what do you say?
你怎么说？
She's not a morning turtle.
她不是早起的乌龟。
- Jackpot!
中了！
Free game tickets.
免费游戏票。
That big, smart banana's mine.
那个大聪明香蕉是我的。
- What, Dicky-- what are you doing?
什么，Dicky——你在干什么？
You cannot keep those tickets.
你不能留着那些票。
- I'm not gonna keep them.
我不会留着它们。
I'm gonna spend them.
我要用掉它们。
We're all gonna spend them.
我们大家都要用掉它们。
- There are so many tickets.
有这么多票。
[gasps]
（惊讶声）
I could deep fry the tickets.
我可以把票炸了。
- And I could ride the rides over and over.
我可以一遍又一遍地坐那些游乐设施。
Uh, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
That's a slippery slope to nowhere.
那是一条通往虚无的滑坡。
Which is a ride I could ride if I had these tickets.
如果我有这些票，我就可以坐那个叫“滑坡”的游乐设施。
No, it's wrong.
不，这是不对的。
- Dawn's right!
- 道恩说得对！
We don't want to wind up like The Dozer.
我们不想变得像多泽那样。
He probably started by stealing carnival tickets,
他可能一开始只是偷嘉年华的票，
now he's bulldozing that kid right into the wall.
现在他直接把那孩子推到墙上了。
- Ricky's right.
- 里基说得对。
So give me the tickets.
所以把票给我。
- No, me! - No, me!
- 不，给我！ - 不，给我！
- No, me! - No, me.
- 不，给我！ - 不，给我。
- It's not what it looks like.
- 不是你们想的那样。
- It's never what it looks like with you four.
- 对你们四个来说，从来都不是表面看起来的那样。
But don't worry, you'll plenty of time
但别担心，你们会有足够的时间
to sort it all out
来理清这一切
when you're in detention this Saturday.
当你们这周六被关禁闭的时候。
- Ooh! Ah...
哦！啊...
Saturday's not gonna work.
周六不行。
We have a carnival thing.
我们有个嘉年华活动。
- Not...
不再...
any...
任何...
more.
更多。
I ran out of words.
我词穷了。
- Great!
太好了！
The one year we get to be the oldest kids
我们唯一一年能成为嘉年华上最大的孩子，
at the carnival, we don't get to go!
我们却去不了！
- Speak for yourselves.
你们自己说吧。
I'm one failed math test away from being right back here
我只差一次数学考试不及格就能
next year.
明年再回到这里了。
Who's a smart one now?
现在谁是聪明的那一个？
[upbeat music]
- ♪ ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- This is something I never thought I'd see.
- 这是我从未想过会看到的场景。
The joint, the slammer,
那个联合的地方，那个监狱，
the big house,
那个大房子，
the pokey, the clink,
那个拘留所，那个牢房，
the gray bar hotel.
那个灰条酒店。
- Ooh, sounds fancy.
- 哦，听起来很豪华。
- We're in jail!
- 我们被关进监狱了！
- Sorry, kids. You did the crime.
- 对不起，孩子们。你们犯了罪。
Now you have to do the time.
现在你们必须承担后果。
- No! Dicky did the crime,
- 不！迪基犯了罪，
Nicky agreed to it, I was on the fence,
尼基同意了，我犹豫不决，
and Ricky didn't stop us.
而瑞奇没有阻止我们。
- Yeah! So he's really the only one
- 对！所以他才是唯一
who should be in here.
应该在这里的人。
- I'm so ashamed.
- 我感到非常羞愧。
- Well, you got into this together,
- 好吧，你们一起陷入这个困境，
so you're gonna have to get through it together.
所以你们得一起度过这个难关。
And if it makes you feel any better,
如果这能让你们感觉好点，
your father and I aren't gonna be having any fun, either.
你们的父亲和我也不会有任何乐趣。
We're gonna be running the Get Sporty game booth all day.
我们一整天都要在‘运动乐园’游戏摊位上忙碌。
- Anne! They're deep frying everything down there.
安妮！他们在下面炸一切东西。
Look at my sunglasses.
看看我的太阳镜。
- Oh.
哦。
- Oh. Working hard, huh?
哦。工作很努力，是吧？
How's your vision, Dad? - [laughs]
你的视力怎么样，爸爸？
- 20/delicious.
20/美味。
- No, Tom! You cannot eat that.
- 不行，汤姆！你不能吃那个。
- Oh, you're right. I need them to see. [chuckles]
- 哦，你说得对。我需要它们来看东西。[轻笑]
- Oh!
- 哦！
See you on the outside.
外面见。
Just go ahead and eat them!
尽管去吃吧！
- That should be us out there deep frying things that have no business being deep fried.
- 我们应该在外面炸那些根本不该被油炸的东西。
- I guess we're just gonna have to try and forget about that carnival.
- 我想我们只能试着忘记那个嘉年华了。
[kids screaming, rollercoaster whooshing]
[孩子们尖叫，过山车呼啸]
Oh, are you kidding me?
哦，你在开玩笑吧？
The Slippery Slope to Nowhere
通往虚无的滑坡
is right outside the window?
就在窗外吗？
- This is torture.
这是折磨。
- I can't believe I'm stuck in this hoosegow.
我真不敢相信我被困在这个监狱里。
- Yeah, we're all in this moose cow.
是啊，我们都困在这个牛圈里。
- Hoosegow. - I don't know whose cow.
监狱。
You're the one who brought it up.
我不知道是谁的牛。
- Knock it off!
是你先提起的。
Mom's right. We need to stick together.
别说了！
[overlapping chatter]
妈妈说得对，我们需要团结一致。
- Here come the other inmates.
其他囚犯来了。
Don't let them see your fear.
别让他们看到你的恐惧。
It's The Dozer.
那是推土机。
He's serving the 18th Saturday
他正在服刑第18个星期六
of a 24-Saturday sentence.
为期24个星期六的刑期。
- I know her!
我认识她！
That's Texting Tina.
那是发短信蒂娜。
She's in for texting in class.
她因为在课堂上发短信而入狱。
They say she's got the fastest thumbs in three counties.
据说她是三个县里发短信最快的人。
- Uh-oh! Don't look now.
哎呀！别看现在。
Here comes Johnny Meatballs.
约翰尼肉丸子来了。
Nobody knows what he's in for, but...
没人知道他是因为什么被抓的，但是...
rumor has it...
传闻说...
it has something to do with meatballs.
这事儿跟肉丸子有关。
- I would hope so.
- 那我倒希望如此。
- Look at all them.
- 看看他们。
The bad kids.
那些坏孩子。
- What are you lookin' at?
- 你看什么看？
- Oh-- - The bad kids.
- 哦——那些坏孩子。
- He didn't mean that, Mr. Meatballs.
- 他不是那个意思，肉丸子先生。
- It's Mr. Onatoppa-Bascetti to you.
- 对你来说，我是奥纳托帕-巴塞蒂先生。
- [chuckles nervously] Mr. Onatoppa-Bascetti.
- [紧张地轻笑] 奥纳托帕-巴塞蒂先生。
Is that Italian?
那是意大利名字吗？
- Greek-Italian.
- 希腊-意大利混血。
Mother Greek, father Italian.
母亲是希腊人，父亲是意大利人。
- Oh? You must tan beautifully.
- 哦？那你一定晒得很漂亮。
- I do!
- 确实如此！
[all sigh]
[大家都叹气]
- That was weirdly terrifying!
- 那真是奇怪又吓人！
- Yeah, why was he so intense about his tan?
- 是啊，他为什么对晒黑这么在意？
- Okay, we just need to keep our heads down
- 好吧，我们今天剩下的时间只需要低调行事
for the rest of the day.
在今天剩下的时间里
- Hey! - [yells]
嘿！
- You're in my seat.
你坐了我的位子。
- I am so sorry!
非常抱歉！
[exhales]
（呼气声）
[kids screaming, rollercoaster whooshing]
（孩子们尖叫，过山车呼啸）
- This is gonna be a long day.
这将是很漫长的一天。
♪
- Tom, this is some of our most expensive merchandise.
汤姆，这些是我们最贵的商品之一。我以为我们要处理掉的是那批搞错的
I thought we were giving away this botched order of
泡沫手指，上面印着‘布伦弗丹科斯’。
foam fingers that say Brenver Doncos.
泡沫手指，上面写着‘布伦弗顿唐科斯’。
- Then no one will come.
那没人会来。
This way...
这样一来...
they all will come.
他们都会来。
- Uh, and then they will all leave
然后他们都会带着我们的东西离开。
with all of our stuff.
哦，不，但这就是聪明之处，安妮。
- Oh, no, but that's the genius, Anne.
我们会卖掉很多学校的门票，但没人能赢。
We'll sell a bunch of tickets for the school, but no one's gonna win.
这个绳梯扭得这么厉害，根本不可能爬上去。
This rope ladder is so twisty, it's impossible.
这就是为什么它叫做‘不可能的扭绳梯’。
That's why it's called The Impossible Twisty Rope Ladder.
当我在店里试的时候，我就像，‘哇！哇！哇！我怎么什么都赢不了？’
When I tried it out at the store, I was all, like, "Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
我在店里试的时候，我就像，“哇！哇！哇！
Why can't I win anything?"
我怎么什么都赢不了？”
- Well, it better be impossible
那最好是不可能的
because we are not giving away a $400 tent.
因为我们不打算送出一顶400美元的帐篷。
- [scoffs] - Or a Jet Ski!
或者一艘水上摩托！
We don't even carry these things! You would have to buy it in order to give it away.
我们甚至不卖这些东西！你必须先买才能送出去。
- Anne, ju-- just watch.
安妮，你——你看着就好。
Hey, uh, Mae! [clears throat]
嘿，呃，梅！[清嗓子]
You wanna try your luck at The Impossible Twisty Rope Ladder?
你想试试不可能的扭曲绳梯吗？
- Sure, why not?
当然，为什么不呢？
- There we go. [chuckles]
好了，开始了。[轻笑]
I hope she's not a sore loser.
我希望她不是个输不起的人。
[bells rings]
[铃声响起]
- Yay! I won! - What?
耶！我赢了！- 什么？
- Please don't take the Jet Ski. Please don't take the Jet Ski. Please don't take the Jet Ski. - I'll take the Jet Ski.
请不要拿走喷气滑雪板。请不要拿走喷气滑雪板。请不要拿走喷气滑雪板。- 我要拿走喷气滑雪板。
- You know what? I probably just set it up wrong.
你知道吗？我可能只是设置错了。
Okay? I-I--I'll just fix it before anyone else gets in line.
好吗？我-我——我会在其他人排队之前修好它。
- Hey, everybody!
嘿，大家！
This is the easiest game ever!
这是有史以来最简单的游戏！
It's not twisty or impossible.
它既不扭曲也不困难。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Is that a picture of my mother's farm?
那是我妈妈的农场的照片吗？
- Oh, oh, Anne, Anne, Anne, don't worry.
- 哦，哦，安妮，安妮，安妮，别担心。
Kids don't care about real estate.
孩子们不在乎房地产。
- Mae, I'm gonna win you a farm.
- 梅，我要为你赢一个农场。
- Psst! Ricky...
- 嘘！里奇...
- Yes, Dawn? - Get off my lap.
- 是的，道恩？ - 从我腿上下来。
- Yes, Dawn.
- 是的，道恩。
- Good morning, detention-ites.
- 早上好，被拘留者们。
Sorry for my good mood, but look what I won.
抱歉我心情好，但看看我赢了什么。
- [chuckles] No glasses.
- [轻笑] 没戴眼镜。
He got one of the stupid ones.
他拿到了一个蠢的。
- Anyhoo, you all know the rules.
- 总之，你们都知道规矩。
No electronic devices. [all groan]
不许使用电子设备。[众人叹气]
- Uh, no sir, I actually don't know the rules
- 呃，不，先生，我其实不知道规矩
because I've never been in here before.
因为我以前从没来过这里。
[laughs] Just wanted to point that out
[笑] 只是想向大家指出这一点。
to everyone. - Phone.
- 手机。
- But...
- 但是...
what if there's...
如果有什么...
you know...
你知道...
an emergency?
紧急情况怎么办？
- What kind of emergency?
- 什么样的紧急情况？
- Yeah, what kind of emergency?
- 对啊，什么样的紧急情况？
- No emergency.
- 没有紧急情况。
Here, take my phone. Take everyone's phone!
来，拿我的手机。拿大家的手机！
We're all doomed!
我们都完蛋了！
- Is she phantom texting?
- 她在幻觉中发短信吗？
- OMG.
- 我的天。
What am I supposed to do with no phone?
没有手机我该怎么办？
Angry face, angry face, pile of poop!
生气的脸，生气的脸，一堆便便！
- All right...
- 好吧...
this week's punishment is a sweet one!
这周的惩罚可真是甜蜜的！
[chuckling]
[轻笑]
You'll see why that's funny in a second.
你马上就会明白为什么这好笑了。
You're gonna be spending your time
你将会花时间
making cotton candy for the carnival.
为嘉年华制作棉花糖。
You see?
明白了吗？
Cotton candy's sweet.
棉花糖是甜的。
Anyhoo!
总之！
Sugar goes in here...
糖从这里进去...
candy comes out of there,
棉花糖从那里出来，
and then you stick 'em, bag 'em, and out the door they go
然后你把它们装进袋子，送出门外
for all the good boys and girls to enjoy.
让所有的好男孩和女孩享受。
Any questions? - Ooh!
有什么问题吗？ - 哦！
- No, you can't eat it.
- 不，你不能吃它。
- Ooh! - No, you can't make a beard out of it. - Ooh!
- 哦！ - 不，你不能用它做胡子。 - 哦！
- Or a mustache. - Ooh!
- 或者小胡子。 - 哦！
- Or bushy eyebrows. - Ooh!
- 或者浓密的眉毛。 - 哦！
- Or armpit hair. - He's done.
- 或者腋毛。 - 他完事了。
- If you can finish all your pallets,
如果你能完成所有的托盘，
you'll be released early from detention
你就可以提前从拘留中释放，
to enjoy the rest of the carnival.
去享受剩下的嘉年华。
Now if you'll excuse me,
现在如果你们不介意，
Shelly and I are going to get our faces painted.
Shelly和我准备去画脸。
- We get to go to the carnival.
我们可以去嘉年华了。
- This is awesome!
这太棒了！
- I'm coming for ya, smart banana.
我来了，聪明的香蕉。
- Come on, guys, if the seven of us work together,
来吧，伙计们，如果我们七个人一起工作，
we can do this.
我们能做到的。
Come on, guys, if the four of us work together,
来吧，伙计们，如果我们四个齐心协力，
we can do this.
我们就能做到。
- And...
然后...
done. - Ugh, how many is that?
完成了。 - 哎，这是第几个了？
- One!
一个！
- I thought we had five.
我以为我们有五个。
- We did!
我们有！
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
- Sending Tina a very angry text.
正在给蒂娜发一条非常生气的短信。
Lightning bolt, frowning face, broken heart.
闪电符号，皱眉脸，破碎的心。
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Guys. So uncool.
- 伙计们，太不酷了。
- Yeah, look, even The Dozer agrees.
- 是啊，看，连The Dozer都同意。
- Oh, he's not agreeing.
- 哦，他不是同意。
He's nodding off.
他在打瞌睡。
- I don't think so.
- 我不这么认为。
- Wait for it...
- 等着看吧...
- [snoring] - And there it is.
- [打呼声] - 看吧，就是这样。
- We're never gonna get to the carnival
- 我们永远也到不了嘉年华，
if the bad kids are just going to eat our hard work.
如果那些坏孩子只是要吃掉我们的辛苦成果。
- Again with the bad kids.
- 又是那些坏孩子。
- Well, come on.
- 拜托，
You are, and everybody knows it.
你就是这样，大家都知道。
No offense.
无意冒犯。
- No offense taken.
- 没冒犯到。
Like how you wouldn't be offended
就像如果我们说你自私，你也不会介意一样。
if we called you selfish.
- 实际上，我们会介意的，
- Well, actually we would be offended
实际上，我们会感到被冒犯
because we're not selfish.
因为我们并不自私。
- Uh, I kinda think you are.
呃，我有点觉得你们是。
And everybody knows it.
而且大家都知道。
- Knows what? There's nothing to know.
知道什么？没什么可知道的。
- Really?
真的吗？
What about when you went on the museum trip... even though you were sick
那次你去博物馆旅行...尽管你生病了
and then got the rest of the school sick?
然后还让学校其他人也生病了？
- Yeah, because of you, I missed my racquetball tournament.
是的，因为你，我错过了我的壁球比赛。
- Wait. You play racquetball? - I think he means meatball.
等等。你打壁球？ - 我想他指的是肉丸。
- Uh, no, I don't.
- 呃，不，我不打。
And I would've been third in the state
而且我本可以在州赛中获得第三名
if I hadn't missed that tournament.
如果我没有错过那场锦标赛的话。
- But we don't really know that.
- 但我们并不真的知道这一点。
You could've had an off day.
你可能那天状态不好。
- You're gonna have an off day.
- 你总会有状态不好的一天。
- Okay, so we may have been selfish that one time.
- 好吧，我们那次可能有点自私。
- You ruined the school concert.
- 你毁了学校的音乐会。
- Okay, two times. - The class election.
- 好吧，两次。 - 班级选举。
- Three times. - The morning announcements.
- 三次。 - 早间公告。
- You know what? We're just gonna go with a handful of times.
- 你知道吗？我们就算是几次吧。
- Even now, all you care about is yourselves and getting out to the carnival.
- 即使现在，你们关心的也只是自己和去嘉年华。
Angry face, thumbs down, two piles of poop.
- 愤怒的脸，大拇指向下，两堆便便。
- She doubled doo-doo'd us.
- 她对我们双倍便便了。
- We're selfish?
- 我们自私？
At least we're doing the detention assignment.
- 至少我们在做留堂作业。
You're not helping at all.
- 你一点忙都没帮。
- That's because we're in here almost every weekend and we never finish Tarian's assignments.
- 那是因为我们几乎每个周末都在这里，而且我们从未完成过Tarian的作业。
- Well, we're gonna finish that assignment
- 好吧，我们要完成那个作业
and get to that carnival.
- 然后去嘉年华。
If you guys aren't gonna help, at least stay out of the way.
如果你们不打算帮忙，至少别碍事。
- Oh, we'll stay out of the way.
哦，我们会待在一边的。
We'll be over here...
我们会在这边...
enjoying the show.
享受这场表演。
- Yeah, and just whatever you do...
是啊，不管你们做什么...
[whispers] Don't wake The Dozer.
别吵醒The Dozer。
- I wonder what happens if we wake The Dozer?
我想知道如果我们吵醒The Dozer会发生什么？
[all chuckle]
（大家都轻声笑）
[fly buzzing]
（苍蝇嗡嗡声）
- I vote for not waking The Dozer.
我赞成不要吵醒The Dozer。
♪ ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
- ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- Tom, you said you set the game up wrong.
- 汤姆，你说你把游戏设置错了。
Can you fix it? - Yes, I can.
你能修好吗？ - 是的，我能。
- [sighs] - I have just the thing.
- [叹气] - 我正好有办法。
[bell rings] - I'll take the toolbox!
[铃声响起] - 我来拿工具箱！
- I no longer have the thing.
- 我不再有那个东西了。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Okay, well, if the ladder isn't the obstacle,
好吧，既然梯子不是障碍，
then we need to be the obstacle.
那么我们需要成为障碍。
- What are you saying, Anne?
- 你在说什么，安妮？
- This.
- 这个。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Hey, you can't poke me!
- 嘿，你不能戳我！
- Our game, our rules! - Yeah!
- 我们的游戏，我们的规则！ - 是的！
- You want my mother's farm?
- 你想要我妈妈的农场？
You've gotta get through me.
你得先过我这关。
[yells] Whoo-hoo!
（大喊）喔呼！
[both laughing]
（两人笑）
- Who's number one now?
现在谁是第一名？
[bell rings]
（铃声响起）
- I am. And I'll take the farm.
是我。而且我要拿下农场。
- Come on, guys, we almost have five pallets filled.
来吧，伙计们，我们几乎装满了五个托盘。
- Uh-oh.
哎呀。
We're running low on sugar.
我们的糖快用完了。
- We have to reload if we want to finish.
如果我们想完成，就必须重新装填。
- But the only bag is on the top shelf!
但唯一的一袋糖在最高层的架子上！
- Top shelf?
最高层的架子？
Why would Principal Tarian put it all the way up there?
塔里安校长为什么要把它放在那么高的地方？
[shimmering tone] - Shelly?
Shelly?
Shelly, you better not be in that sugar again.
Shelly, 你最好不要再碰那些糖了。
Fool me once, Shelly.
Shelly, 被你骗一次就够了。
I'm gonna have to put this out of your reach.
我得把它放得你够不着。
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
Nope!
不！
[grunting]
（咕哝声）
[whistles] Let's go.
（吹口哨）走吧。
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
[shimmering tone]
[闪烁的音调]
- I bet you that's what happened.
- 我打赌这就是发生的事情。
- Well, what are we gonna do?
- 那么，我们该怎么办？
None of us are tall enough
我们中没有人足够高
or strong enough to get that bag down.
或者足够强壮来拿下那个包。
- [sighs] - [snoring]
- [叹气] - [打鼾]
all: The Dozer.
所有人: 推土机。
- But Tina warned us never to wake him.
- 但蒂娜警告我们永远不要叫醒他。
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
- I got this.
- 我来搞定。
- What's that for?
- 这是干什么用的？
- Oh!
- 哦！
I get it. A peace offering.
我明白了，这是和平的表示。
- Or I could do something that makes sense...
- 或者我可以做一些有意义的事...
and use it as a disguise.
用它来伪装。
This way, when he seeks revenge,
这样，当他寻求报复时，
he won't be looking for me.
他不会找我。
He'll be looking for a blue unicorn.
他会找一个蓝色的独角兽。
- Dicky, be careful!
- 迪基，小心点！
I can't watch.
我看不下去。
Tell me what's happening.
告诉我发生了什么。
- They're talking, they're talking...
- 他们在交谈，他们在交谈...
- That sounds positive.
- 听起来是积极的。
- And now they're walking, they're walking...
- 现在他们在走，他们在走...
- That could go either way.
- 这可能有两种结果。
- And now they're leaving...
- 现在他们在离开...
- They're leaving? - Now they're gone...
- 他们离开了？ - 现在他们走了...
- They're gone?
- 他们走了？
Wait!
等等！
So he just took Dicky...
所以他刚刚带走了Dicky...
and you guys didn't do anything?
你们什么都没做吗？
- Well, we would've stopped him,
我们本来会阻止他的，
but we had to tell you what was happening.
但我们得告诉你发生了什么。
- What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
Dicky's disappeared with a desk-smashing madman!
Dicky和一个砸桌子的疯子一起消失了！
- Nicky, Ricky, and Dawn.
Nicky, Ricky, 和 Dawn。
Oh, hey, look!
哦，嘿，看！
There goes Nicky, Ricky, and Dawn.
Nicky, Ricky, 和 Dawn走了。
Nicky, Ricky, and Dawn, get down here!
Nicky, Ricky, 和 Dawn，下来这里！
- What are you doing? - Just trying it out because Dicky's gone!
你们在干什么？我只是试试，因为Dicky走了！
- Check it out.
看看这个。
Nicky, Ricky, and Dawn are panicking.
Nicky, Ricky 和 Dawn 正在慌乱。
- Oh.
哦。
- ♪ Oh-oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- I knew prison life would be tough...
我知道监狱生活会很艰难...
but I never thought we'd lose a brother.
但我从没想到我们会失去一个兄弟。
- We haven't lost him. He's outside with The Dozer.
我们没有失去他。他和The Dozer在外面。
- I can't watch.
我看不下去。
Tell me what's happening.
告诉我发生了什么。
- Okay, The Dozer just picked up a softball.
好的，The Dozer刚刚捡起了一个垒球。
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
He's going to hit Dicky in the head with it.
他要用球砸Dicky的头。
- He just handed it to Dicky. - Oh, no!
他刚刚把球递给了Dicky。
He's going to make Dicky hit himself in the head with it!
他要让Dicky自己用球砸自己的头！
Don't do it, Dicky!
别这么做，Dicky！
- Relax, they're just playing the milk bottle game.
放松，他们只是在玩牛奶瓶游戏。
- It's still not good.
这还是不好。
If Principal Tarian catches Dicky out there,
如果Tarian校长发现Dicky在外面，
the four of us are gonna be in even bigger trouble.
我们四个会有更大的麻烦。
- There you go again, being selfish.
- 你又来了，自私自利。
- Yeah, The Dozer is out there too.
- 是啊，多泽也在外面。
- Well, then, we need to go out there
- 那么，我们需要出去
and get them both back. Here, let's go.
把他们两个都带回来。来，我们走。
- Uh, no.
- 呃，不行。
If you guys get caught,
如果你们被抓到，
you're just gonna be selfish and blame it on us.
你们只会自私地怪罪到我们头上。
You stay, we'll go.
你们留下，我们去。
- Well, we don't trust you, either.
- 好吧，我们也不信任你们。
- Fine, we'll all go.
- 好吧，我们都去。
- Our first prison break.
我们的第一次越狱。
I know exactly what to do!
我知道该怎么做！
Everyone, give me your jackets.
大家，把你们的夹克给我。
I'll tie them together and create a rope for us
我把它们绑在一起，做成一根绳子
to climb down to escape, and get to Dicky and The Dozer.
让我们爬下去逃脱，去找迪基和多泽。
- Or we could just go out that open door.
或者我们可以直接从那扇开着的门出去。
- Or that!
或者那！
[jazzy spy music]
[爵士间谍音乐]
♪ ♪
- Whoa-whoa-whoa! Oh, Shelly, no!
- 哇-哇-哇！哦，Shelly，不行！
No, Shelly.
- 不行，Shelly。
♪ ♪
[thuds] - Yes!
[砰] - 是的！
Finally!
终于！
- Psst! Dicky!
- 嘘！Dicky！
- [exclaims]
- [惊呼]
He knows my name.
他知道我的名字。
- Dicky!
- Dicky！
- Aw, man. It was just you.
- 哎，伙计。原来是你。
- Dicky, come on.
- 迪基，快点。
We have to get back before
我们得在
Principal Tarian knows we're gone.
塔里安校长发现我们不在之前回去。
- Here he comes now!
- 他现在过来了！
- Quick! Hide under this booth!
- 快！躲到这个摊位下面！
- There's no room with all these trolls. - Then just pull them out!
- 这些巨魔太多了，没地方了。 - 那就把它们拉出来！
[whispering] Go, go.
[低语] 快，快。
- Do you think Tarian's gone?
- 你觉得塔里安走了吗？
- He's still there! - Ugh.
- 他还在那儿！ - 呃。
- Who's ready to Whack-A-Troll?
- 谁准备好打巨魔了？
What happened to my trolls?
我的巨魔们怎么了？
- Quick! We gotta be trolls!
- 快！我们得变成巨魔！
[carnival music]
[嘉年华音乐]
[banging]
[敲击声]
- This is all your fault, Dicky.
- 这都是你的错，迪基。
- How is it my fault?
- 怎么是我的错？
- You let The Dozer Dicky-nap you.
- 你让推土机迪基绑架了你。
- No, I didn't! I made a deal with him.
- 不，我没有！我和他做了个交易。
- What deal?
- 什么交易？
- He'll help us with the sugar if I win him the big banana.
- 如果我为他赢得大香蕉，他会帮我们搞定糖。
- And he did!
- 他确实帮了忙！
- He's not a bad kid.
- 他不是个坏孩子。
- You just assumed he was.
- 你只是先入为主地认为他是。
- But the call him The Dozer because he bulldozes people.
- 但他们叫他The Dozer是因为他碾压别人。
- No, they call him The Dozer
- 不，他们叫他The Dozer
because he's always falling asleep.
因为他总是打瞌睡。
all: Ohh!
所有人: 哦！
- And the reason he's falling asleep
- 他打瞌睡的原因
is because he helps take care of his baby brother.
是因为他帮忙照顾他的小弟弟。
- That's who the banana's for!
- 那个大香蕉就是为他准备的！
all: Aww!
大家：哎呀！
♪ ♪
- But what about that kid you pinned to the wall?
那个被你按在墙上的孩子呢？
- I was helping him hang a poster for his lost kitten.
我是在帮他挂一张寻找丢失小猫的海报。
all: Aww!
大家：哎呀！
- Come on! Can't you hit somebody else?
拜托！你就不能打别人吗？
- No.
不行。
- Ooh! This looks fun.
哦！这看起来很有趣。
I'm next.
下一个是我。
- Time to go!
该走了！
[banging]
- It's not working!
- 这不管用！
- No refunds.
- 不退款。
- So it turns out, farm life isn't as fun as you think.
- 结果证明，农场生活并不像你想的那么有趣。
- Have you ever milked a chicken?
- 你挤过鸡的奶吗？
- Okay, okay, the truth is,
- 好吧，好吧，事实是，
the farm wasn't really ours to give.
- 这个农场其实不是我们能给的。
- Picture this!
- 想象一下！
Mae's Get Sporty. - Yeah!
- 梅的体育用品店。 - 是的！
- But I want the farm.
- 但我想要农场。
- You can't have the farm!
你不能拥有这个农场！
- Don't make me lawyer up.
别逼我请律师。
- Wait, wait, wait a minute!
等等，等等，等一下！
So if The Dozer's not a bad kid...
所以如果The Dozer不是坏孩子...
are any of you bad kids?
你们中有谁是坏孩子吗？
- Nope. I only use my phone all the time
没有。我只是整天用手机
because my best friend moved to New Zealand.
因为我最好的朋友搬到了新西兰。
- Oh! Let me guess.
哦！让我猜猜。
You probably have some heartwarming story
你可能有一个感人的故事
about why you're called Johnny Meatballs.
关于为什么你被称为Johnny Meatballs。
- Why can't I just like meatballs?
- 为什么我就不能喜欢肉丸呢？
- Meatballs are good.
- 肉丸挺好的。
- Look, guys, we're really sorry we misjudged you,
- 听着，伙计们，我们真的很抱歉之前误会了你，
and I'm glad we're getting this chance to know each other,
- 我很高兴我们有机会互相了解，
but we gotta get back in there before Tarian catches us.
- 但我们得赶紧回去，不然塔里安会发现我们的。
- Relax, Dawn.
- 放松点，Dawn。
We're right here.
- 我们就在这儿。
We totally made it.
- 我们完全做到了。
Oh, no!
- 哦，不！
- We must've left the machine on!
- 我们一定是忘了关机器！
- What do we do now?
我们现在该怎么办？
- I know exactly what to do.
我知道该怎么做。
I've had dreams about this.
我梦到过这种情况。
I'm goin' cloud tastin'.
我要去尝尝云的味道。
- Anybody got any other ideas?
有人有其他主意吗？
Then let's go cloud tastin'.
那我们去尝尝云吧。
- Are you almost done with the--
你快好了吗？
sweet spun sugar!
甜蜜的棉花糖！
What happened here?
这里发生了什么？
[all groaning]
（大家都呻吟着）
You dumped the whole bag in, didn't you?
你把整袋都倒进去了，对吧？
[all groaning]
（大家都在呻吟）
And then you ate it, didn't you?
然后你吃了它，对吧？
[all groaning]
（大家都在呻吟）
Well, I guess none of you
好吧，我想你们今天
are going to that carnival today.
都不会去那个嘉年华了。
[all groaning]
（大家都在呻吟）
Now, if you'll excuse me...
现在，如果你们不介意的话...
Shelly is saving my place in line at
Shelly正在帮我排队
The Slippery Slope To Nowhere.
在‘无底滑坡’那里。
- Principal Tarian, wait.
校长塔里安，等等。
It was us four who had the idea to eat the cotton candy.
是我们四个想出了吃棉花糖的主意。
- They had nothing to do with it.
他们与此事无关。
- Wow.
哇。
That must be the truth...
那一定是真的...
because I know you Harpers are way too selfish
因为我知道你们哈珀家的人太自私了，
to take the blame for someone else.
不会为别人承担责任的。
- It was a handful of incidents!
这只是几件小事！
- Well...
嗯...
I guess you three are free to go.
我想你们三个可以走了。
And I'd get out quick if I were you.
如果我是你，我会尽快离开。
You don't want to end up like these bad kids.
你不会想变成这些坏孩子的样子。
[synthesizer music]
[合成器音乐]
- Thanks.
- 谢谢。
That was really cool of you.
你真是太酷了。
- I guess you're not as selfish as we thought.
- 我想你并不像我们想的那么自私。
- I guess we all learned something that day.
- 我想那天我们都学到了一些东西。
People aren't always as you see them.
人们并不总是你看到的那样。
They're not just the bad kids.
他们不仅仅是那些坏孩子。
♪ ♪
They're...
他们是...
- A good big brother.
一个好大哥。
- Girl who misses her best friend.
一个想念最好朋友的女孩。
- And a potentially good racquetball player who just likes meatballs.
一个可能成为优秀壁球运动员的人，只是喜欢肉丸。
- We lost our chance at being the big kids at the carnival,
我们失去了在嘉年华上成为大孩子的机会，
but you know what we did get?
但你知道我们得到了什么吗？
New friends!
新朋友！
- And stomach aches.
还有胃痛。
Really bad stomach aches.
真的很严重的胃痛。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ 耶耶，耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪